# **BYRON POLLEY**

Johannesburg, South Africa | byronpolley@live.com | +27 83 286 5231

# **Skills Summary**

Full Stack Engineer currently located in Johannesburg, South Africa. I have a multidisciplinary background in user experience design, devops and software engineering. I am enthralled by serverless as I think it yields the highest potential for being a front runner in the digital space.

#### Education

# Monash University

Bachelor of Computer & Information Sciences | June 2012 – November 2015 Graduated in 2015 with a major in Application Development & Networking and a minor in Business Systems. Course has a strong focus on security, object-orientated design and data structures / algorithms. Primary language of development was Java.

### **Experience**

## SovTech | sovtech.com

Full Stack Engineer (January 2020 – Present)

My role here involves software engineering and DevOps using AWS. React, Node.js, GraphQL and serverless are the commonly used technologies. I am lead frontend in my team and mentor junior developers. I have been enjoying the CI / CD aspect of this job.

# Cavalry | hellocavalry.com

Frontend Engineer (April 2018 – December 2020)

After joining the team, I not only pioneered the transition from PHP to Angular but also improved business practices by introducing tools like Slack and 1Password which increased productivity immensely. Notable projects included the development of an Aldriven insurance quotation bot and a funeral policy PWA for AIG.

#### The Bread | thebread.co.za

Frontend Developer (June 2016 – March 2018)

Predominantly developed eCommerce offerings and interactive applications such as touch screen kiosks and other marketing software. I was responsible for overseeing the UX designs and ensuring smooth designer / developer handover.